revenuewire.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy | RevenueWire Inc.

**Effective Date: August 28, 2015**

RevenueWire Inc. ("RevenueWire") is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you may provide to us when using any of our online services such as when you use our website: www.revenuewire.com. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat information we receive when you transmit data to RevenueWire.

Revenuewire, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.revenuewire.com](http://www.revenuewire.com/).

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@revenuewire.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

## Information Collection

When you submit information to open an account to either offer your digital download product for sale through the RevenueWire services or you open an account to purchase or promote any products that are being offered by RevenueWire, we may collect personal information including without limitation your name, address, email address, and phone number for the purpose of establishing an account with RevenueWire, the collection of billing information for transaction processing, and recording the transactions when you engage in activities on our web site or through the RevenueWire services. If and when we use a payment processing merchant, we ensure that the same strict privacy criteria are in place.

When creating an account as an Affiliate or Merchant on our site, if you wish to have payments wired to your bank account, we will ask you to submit Bank Account information to us in order to facilitate these payments. The Bank Account information you submit to us is sensitive information and is therefore protected by us using industry-standard SSL Encryption.

From time to time, and provided that we have your consent, we may also send you electronic mail containing information about product updates, new product offerings and other information that may interest you. At any time, you may opt-out of receiving email from us, either by clicking the Unsubscribe link in the applicable email, or by sending an email with your request to privacy@revenuewire.com, and including 'UNSUBSCRIBE' in the subject line.

We respect your privacy and value your trust. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We will never sell, rent, lease, or give your information to a third party unless required to do so by law.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We may also disclose your personal information if RevenueWire is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to RevenueWire's collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes as outlined herein.

Any information that you post to a community-based website, personal entry site, chat room, public bulletin, blog or forum is available to all users of that site. RevenueWire cannot control, nor is it responsible for the use, disclosure, or dissemination of such information by any third parties. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy@revenuewire.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Web Site Usage

We may collect and record information that is related to the interaction between an Internet user and the RevenueWire website(s). Interactions may include, without limitation, ad content/banner delivery, counting click-throughs on an ad/banner, tracking web page views following a click-through, and sales tracking. Other information that we may collect includes IP addresses and Web site usage information when you access our online services. This non-personally identifiable information helps RevenueWire in evaluating the functionality of our services in order to identify areas on how we can improve our services to our clients. This information also assists RevenueWire in reporting relevant data on advertisements and sales to all our applicable clients.

## How Information Is Used When Collected

  * To process, validate and verify purchases through the RevenueWire services.
  * To ensure proper payments to applicable business partners such as affiliates, advertisers, or software publishers
  * To contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of the information provided by you.
  * To register you as a client and open an account for you with RevenueWire either as a merchant or affiliate partner.
  * To open and maintain a support account for you.
  * To send email notifications about updates to existing product offerings or services, to inform you of new product offerings or services, or to update you on any changes to this Privacy Policy.
  * To send information on special offers, or to obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide added products and services.
  * To enable RevenueWire or its clients to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs, suggestions, or recommendations.
  * To conduct applicable business such as invoicing or making payments to business partners.
  * To contact you should there be any changes to your account with RevenueWire.
  * To enforce our service agreement or terms of use.
  * If required to be disclose by applicable law.

## Access to Personal Information

Once you have submitted your personal information to our web site, we provide you with the opportunity to access that information in order to update, delete or correct it. If you have created a profile as a Merchant or Affiliate, you may login to your account with us and update the information there. You may update your email address from the 'Profile' link, and your other information from the 'Setup' link.

If you did not create a profile on www.revenuewire.com, you may send us an email with your request to access your information at [privacy@revenuewire.com](mailto:privacy@revenuewire.com).

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Tracking Technologies

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Revenuewire, Inc. and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings, and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

## Behavioral Targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Links

We may offer links from our website to other third party websites which may be hosted by our business partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and RevenueWire makes no representation or warranties as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit.

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Security

The personal information that is collected by RevenueWire is stored in limited access servers. RevenueWire takes reasonable precautions to protect the information that has been collected, and to safeguard the servers where such information is stored.

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at privacy@revenuewire.com.

## Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you in order to reflect our practices and provide greater protection for your information. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted promptly here, on the RevenueWire Home Page, or in a prominent location or place that we deem appropriate so that you are aware of any changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back periodically. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.

## Acceptance of Terms

By using the RevenueWire services or accessing the RevenueWire web site you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this Privacy Policy.

## Contact Us

RevenueWire, Inc.  
102-3962 Borden St.  
Victoria, BC V8P 3H8  
Canada
